<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ahmed Tchagnaou</title><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/</link><description>Recent content on Ahmed Tchagnaou</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>© {year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://atchagnaou.me/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atchagnaou.me/en/resume/</guid><description>Résumé I am a student in Big Data Management and Analytics. I love Web Development, Data Analysis and Artificial Intelligence. I'm currently looking for end-of-training internship. You can find some of my projects on the page "Work" and on my Github page. Skills Languages Python, R, SQL, Javascript, Java Web Development Flask, Bootstrap, ReactJS, Sass Data Visualization tool Tableau Desktop, Power BI Database Systems MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQL Server, MongoDB Autres Git, Docker, Azure, Hadoop Work Experience Internship - Web Developer ORTECH Intelligent Systems, Blois-France - (June 2021 ~ August 2021) Implementation of a monitoring and control system (Administration module) Implementation of a Restful API with Flask Implementation of a frontend app with ReactJS communicating with the API Users management Access management Logs management Internship - Cloud Consultant MANSTRICT CONSULTING, Paris-France - (June 2020 ~ July 2020) Configuration and management of an on-premise cloud.</description></item><item><title>Blog App</title><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/blog/</guid><description>This project is a web application that let users to create posts. Users can follow each other and react to the posts of the users they are following by adding comments. This project was built with Java Enterprise Edition, Bootstrap, JQuery and MySQL. The code source is available on Github : Blog App</description></item><item><title>Fruits and Vetgetables Recognition</title><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/fruits-and-vegetables/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/fruits-and-vegetables/</guid><description>This project is a web application to test an image recognition model trained on various fruits and vegetables with Azure Custom Vision. Follow this link to test the model. This project was built with Azure Custom Vision, Svelte and Bulma.</description></item><item><title>KNN from scratch</title><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/knn-iris/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/knn-iris/</guid><description>In this project, we implemented the KNN algorithm from scratch on the iris dataset. We implemented the following features : Euclidean distance computing Train et test split Computing of metrics like precision and recall Confusion matrix Cross Validation The project has been implemented in Java and it is available on Github : KNN</description></item><item><title>Water Quality Prediction</title><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/water-potability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/water-potability/</guid><description>This project is a classification problem. We have trained a model to determine if a water source is potable or not by providing some measures like : ph, chloramine, sulfate, ... You can find the notebook on Kaggle.</description></item></channel></rss>