<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Works on Ahmed Tchagnaou</title><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/</link><description>Recent content in Works on Ahmed Tchagnaou</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>© {year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blog App</title><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/blog/</guid><description>This project is a web application that let users to create posts. Users can follow each other and react to the posts of the users they are following by adding comments. This project was built with Java Enterprise Edition, Bootstrap, JQuery and MySQL. The code source is available on Github : Blog App</description></item><item><title>Fatal Encounters</title><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/fatal-encounters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/fatal-encounters/</guid><description>The goal of this post is to explore the Fatal Encounters dataset. First, we defined a set of questions. Then we created graphs to answer these questions and finally, we commented on these graphs. Fatal Encounters documents non-police deaths that occur when police are present or are precipitated by police action or presence. It documents all available records for all 50 states of USA, back to 2000. The general ouline of this post is as follows : Part 1 : Exploration Visualisation based on race Visualization based on state Other visualizations Part 2 : Summary Part 1 : Exploration 1.</description></item><item><title>Fruits and Vetgetables Recognition</title><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/fruits-and-vegetables/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/fruits-and-vegetables/</guid><description>This project is a web application to test an image recognition model trained on various fruits and vegetables with Azure Custom Vision. Follow this link to test the model. This project was built with Azure Custom Vision, Svelte and Bulma.</description></item><item><title>KNN from scratch</title><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/knn-iris/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/knn-iris/</guid><description>In this project, we implemented the KNN algorithm from scratch on the iris dataset. We implemented the following features : Euclidean distance computing Train et test split Computing of metrics like precision and recall Confusion matrix Cross Validation The project has been implemented in Java and it is available on Github : KNN</description></item><item><title>Water Quality Prediction</title><link>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/water-potability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atchagnaou.me/en/work/water-potability/</guid><description>This project is a classification problem. We have trained a model to determine if a water source is potable or not by providing some measures like : ph, chloramine, sulfate, ... You can find the notebook on Kaggle.</description></item></channel></rss>